I'm a personal trainer based in Berlin and I stumbled across
Chase or BlockBlock
Studio through a friend of mine who worked with Chase before
so I hopped on a
call with him and we talked about my my goals my vision for
the website and I
felt like I was understood right off the bat it was a very
familiar vibe to
which made working with Chase a lot more easygoing that's for
sure because
Chase is just an overall great guy who is very patient with
you and this came we
worked together during a time where I had a lot going on
personally and he was
very patient with me making sure I was staying on track and
guiding me for the
whole process without making me feel overwhelmed which was
the great
highlight for me his communication skills are great here he's
very
responsive uh it's a big plus um i had a lot of ideas i
wanted to implement into the website and
he went through the these ideas these visions i had for the
website and made sure that they fit
the brand identity and never really dismissed any ideas so
that was um yeah a great great highlight
of mine he uh through the whole process i just felt seen i
felt like um i felt heard i felt
like i was being involved in the whole process and most
importantly i felt genuinely taken care of
and that isn't the norm nowadays anymore i would say what i
love most about the website is not just
another template everyone anyone can throw together there's a
lot of intention that went
into it we focus on the customer journey the the user
experience and made sure that
yeah the website the brand identity looked authentic and
memorable so if you're looking
for someone who takes care of you who focuses on the details
and who yeah who's there for you
who's responsive you're definitely in the right place with
Chase or Blok Blok Studio in this case.